Find the B in Fixing in Fixing Deformation of the Garment.
In the document Fixing Deformation of the Garment, I will drag it into the 2D or 3D window.
In the fire simulation, the clothing has some twisted deformation.
Usually, the twisted part of the clothing is caused by the error of the sewing line.
In order to solve this problem, you need to adjust the sewing line.
Because the panel in the 2D window is flat,
it is difficult to find the wrong place of the sewing line.
In the 3D tool bar, select Edit Sewing Line Tool.
In the twisted part, left-click to select.
In the 2D window, the sewing line will be selected.
Here is the clothing twisted deformation due to the cross-section of the sewing line.
In the 2D window, right-click on the wrong sewing line.
In the table of contents, select Swap Sewing Line.
Switch the sewing line direction to the same.
And activate the simulation to see.
Rotate the view to the back view.
Left-click on the twisted sewing line.
In the 2D window, check.
This is because the sewing line is twisted.
The 3D sewing curve deformation caused by the wrong position.
In the 2D window, use the Edit Sewing Line Tool.
Along the outline of the panel.
The wrong sewing line is moved to the correct position.
Activate the simulation to observe the adjustment.
Repeat the above operation.
Move the wrong sewing line to the correct position.
Activate the simulation.
Check the situation after adjustment.
In the 2D window, we see theВы
I have toalgicly insert the
knitting by crossing through the stitch.
operation.
In the 2D window, we see the
ICA
of the端
of the
knitted